previously on prison break:
越狱前情提要
Give me the number for a sundown tel,please?
请帮我查下Sundown旅馆的电话
Got one in gila,new mexico.
找到一家 在Gila 新墨西哥州
6-3,Tomorrow.
6月3号 明天
Who is this?
你是谁?
I think you already know.
你应该知道
But if I buried someone in my own backyard,I'd think about it all the time.
要是我杀了人 在自家后院藏尸 我会时刻惦记着
Let me and my family disappear and in return,I'll keep your little secret.
放过我和我的家人 我会帮你保密
I know it's not how you wanted this to play out.
我知道你不想这样
Sometimes things happen that are just...out of your control.
但有时事态的发展... 你也没法控制
I'll see you soon,michael.
我们马上会见面的 Michael
It just may be sooner than you think.
可能比你想象的要快
You can't be here!
你不能来这
Where's your sister?I need to see maricruz.
你姐姐呢? 我要见Maricruz
The wedding's at 2:30.
婚礼2点半就要开始了
Maricruz,she told him,"no." Can you believe that?
Maricruz 居然对他说'不' 难以置信
Go on,get your girl.
去吧,去找你的女孩
Lj!
LJ!
Both of you face down,now! Please...
- 你们俩都趴下 快点! - 求你了...
Suspect in custody.
疑犯被捕
Possible I.D.: Lincoln burrows.
疑犯身份 Lincoln Burrows
You're going to tell me where you stashed westmoreland's money
告诉我Westomoreland 的钱藏在哪了?
or I'm gonna pluck you like a chicken,stitch-by-stitch.
否则我就一下一下把你拔成秃鸡
tribune,kansas
Tribune 堪萨斯州
for a millionaire,you travel light.
作为一个百万富翁,你挺低调
What is this?
这是什么?
it's for my blood pressure.
测血压的
Looky what I found.
看我找到了什么
Guess ms.Hollander liked to beat some meat.
看来Hollander太太喜欢剁肉陷啊
Maybe a couple of whacks in the temple with this will help you remember where you put the money.
用这个剁剁你 也许就能想起钱的下落了
Hey,we've been beating his ass all night.He ain't coming off the goods.
嘿 我们都打了一夜了 他什么也不说
We need to do something different.
得想点新招
It don't matter what you do to me.
不管你们怎么对我
I ain't talking.
我什么也不会说
Well,I ain't stopping till I get what I came for.
达不到目的 我绝不会停手
not again.
再听一遍怎么样
now you're gonna tell me where that money is,or i'm gonna read it on your tombstone?
告诉我钱的下落 我看你是不见棺材不落泪
okay...
好吧...
okay.
好吧
We'll give you a little clue.
给你点线索
It ain't here.
钱不在这
chicago,illinois fbi field office
芝加哥 伊利诺斯州 外勤办事处
confirmed,burrows is in custody.
确认Burrows被捕
Unbelievable.
难以置信
He made it all the way to arizona.
他跑到亚利桑那州去了
Another day,he would have been gone.
再晚一天 他就跑了
You find mahone?
找到Mahone了么?
No.
没有
Keep trying to call,it goes straight to voicemail.
打电话 总是接到留言机
This is alexander mahone.
我是Alexander Mahone
Please leave a message.
请留言
mr.Kim.
Kim 先生
Mr.Kellerman.
Kellerman 先生
Lincoln burrows is in custody.
Lincoln Burrows被捕了
That's the reason I called.
所以给你打个电话
Who has him?
他在谁手上?
Wilcox,arizona pd.
Wilcox亚利桑那警局
We need to extricate him,right away.
我们得马上把他弄出来
Where's mr.Mahone?
Mahone先生在哪 ?
I'm getting in touch with him right now,but I can take care of this one myself.
正在联系他 不过这次我就能处理
This is why we hired mr.Mahone.
雇Mahone先生来就是做这个的
He's the official face here.
由他出面
Don't worry.This won't be official,and there won't be any questions.
别急,这事不会公开也不会有疑问
Of course,there will.
疑问当然
Just make sure no one's left to answer them.
只要不留下能回答问题的人就行了
willcox,arizona
Willcox 亚利桑那州
My son had nothing to do with this,please.
我儿子与这事无关
A judge will decide that.
法官会判决的
You call ahead? Yeah,phoenix is sending backup.
- 你汇报过了? - 嗯,费城正在调后援
I don't think it's one of ours,jimmy.
这不是我们的人,Jimmy
What the hell?!
见鬼?!
come on!
快点
Run,run!
跑,快跑
Come here!
过来
Okay,calm down.
没事,冷静
you y that again... who the hell are you?!
- 你敢再来一次... - 你到底是谁?!
We're on your side!
我们是你这边的
We're with your father.
你父亲的人
chicago,illinois o'hare international airport
芝加哥 伊利诺斯州 O'Hare 国际机场
mahone,lincoln burrows has been apprehended.
Mahone,Lincoln Burrows被捕了
Where? Arizona.
- 在哪? - 亚利桑那州
I'm on my way and I need your talents,on the ground as well.
我正赶去,我需要你助我一臂之力
I'll get there as soon as I can.
我会尽快赶到
I don't think you heard me.
你听懂没有
Get to arizona.
去亚利桑那州
I'm this close to scofield.
我马上就抓到Scofield了
We have a bird in the hand.
我有线索,能把他引出来
Yeah,well,so might I.
嗯,我也有
You wanted me to figure out scofield's rendezvous with tancredi?
想要我查出 Scofield和Tancredi在哪接头么?
It's happening today...
他们今天见面
and I'm sitting right on top of it.
我就快得手了
www.huodidao.com
-= 火地岛互动英语 http://www.huodidao.com =-
prison break
越狱 第二季第10集
gila,new mexico
Gila 新墨西哥州
trinadad,colorado
Trinadad 科罗拉多州
what are you looking at?
看什么看?
Where are we? It doesn't matter.
- 这是哪? - 这不重要
You're safe here.
你在这很安全
You can take a seat.
坐吧
I ain't doing a thing until I see my dad.
见到我爸爸之前,我什么都不做
All I can tell you is he's on his way.
我只能告诉你他在路上了
His flight lands in an hour.
飞机再有1小时就降落了
Why should I trust you,lady?
小姐,我凭什么信你?
I don't see you have much of a choice.
我觉得你别无选择
I could drop you back off with the cops if you'd prefer.
如果你愿意我可以把你们还给警察
You have somewhere else to be? Matter of fact,we do.
- 你有其他的去处? - 确实如此
We can't let you leave.
我们不能放你走
And your father was expecting your brother to be with you.Do you know where he is?
你爸爸希望你们两兄弟在一起 你知道他在哪么?
Do you really think I'm going to answer that?
你以为我会告诉你么?
You need to start cooperating with us,lincoln.
Lincoln你得跟我们合作
We're only trying to help.
我们只想帮忙
micheal scofield,escaped from fox river a week ago
Micheal Scofield 一周前从Fox River越狱
No,never seen him.
不,从没见过
Well,if you do,please call me at that number.
要是看见了给我打电话
Will do.
我会的
There's another hotel down the road.
这条路上还有家旅馆
Thanks.
谢谢
yeah?
诶?
You got a fax.
有你的传真
Uh,could you put it under the door,please?
嗯,从门缝塞进来可以吗?
Thank you.
谢谢
1 hour 16781 butterfield road
1小时后 16781 Butterfield 路见
dinosaur,nebraska
Dinosaur 内布拉斯加州
Theresa.
Theresa
It's fernando sucre.
Fernando Sucre的电话
Fernando. Theresa.
- Fernando - Theresa
She's not here. Please don't hang up.
- 她不在 - 求你了,别挂
I'M...I'm so sorry.Please.
我... 我很抱歉,求你了
Just...
我只是...
I need to know something.
只是想问点事
You've got bigger problems than my sister right now.
你自己的处境比我姐姐更麻烦
No,no.Wait.Please.Please.
不,不,等一下,求你了
I need to talk to her.
我要跟她说句话
Please. You can'T.
- 求你了 - 不行
We're leaving this afternoon.
我们下午就走了
Where you going? Ixtapa,mexico.
- 去哪? - 墨西哥的Ixtapa
We won't be back for a week.
要呆一周
We're taking the honeymoon she had planned with hector.
按照她和Hector的原定蜜月计划
She's picking me up in a few hours.
她一会过来接我
What time?
什么时候?
A little before 2:00.
快2点时
she have to call me.Okay.I'll give you the number.
让她给我打电话,我把号码给你
Where are you? Take this number off caller I.D.
- 你在哪? - 就现在我用这个号码
Please,theresa,just have her call me,okay?
Theresa,让她给我打电话,好吗?
I'll be right here.
我就在这等
Hello,sara.
你好,Sara
I wasn't sure you'd come.
你不知道你会不会来
I didn't have a choice.
我别无选择
This isn't going to be easy for you.
这对你并不容易
You said in your message that you had a plan to make this right.
你的留言里说你的计划会成功
I need to know what that is.
我想知道是什么
Yeah,she checked in last night.
对 她昨晚入住的
Was she alone? Yeah.
- 她一个人? - 对
Kelli foster.
Kelli Foster
I put her in room nine.
我给了她9号房
You the guy that was trying to call this morning?
你是早上打电话来的人?
A guy tried to call this morning?
早上有人打电话来?
Yeah.He was trying to send her a fax.
对 有个男的有份传真给她
Did he do it?
传了吗?
Yeah.20 minutes ago.
对 20分钟前
Does the fax have memory?
传真机有记忆功能吗?
I guess so.
我想有
Do you know where that is?
知道这是哪儿吗?
It's five minutes away.
离这儿只有五分钟的路程
Hey,if she comes ck,is there anything you want me to do?
嘿 如果她回来了 要我做什么吗?
She isn't coming back.
她不会回来了
I've arranged for us to get to panama.
我安排大家去巴拿马
We're meeting up with my brother tomorrow.
明天和我哥哥会合
Wait.That's your plan?
等等 这就是你的计划?
To run away to panama with the two most wanted men in america?
和两个美国头号通缉犯 一起逃到巴拿马?
Michael,I came here because I thought you were going to have real answers for me.
Michael 我到这里来 是以为你能给我真正的答案
This is an answer.
这就是答案
And,right now,it's the only one we've got.
而且是我们目前唯一的答案
Running away into the sunset with the man who lied to me?
和一个骗过我的人一起跑路?
Really?
真的?
I mean,did you know about the other guys?
我是说 你了解其他那些人吗?
Did you know that I would be putting t-bag back out on to the street?
你知道我会把T-Bag也放出去吗?
I never meant for that to happen.
我本不想发生那些事
I was doing what I needed to do.
我只是做必须的事情
My brother was going to die. Well,my father's dead.
- 我的哥哥就要死了 - 但我父亲已经死了
I am sorry about your father.
我为你的父亲难过
I'm sorry for a lot of things.
很多事情我都很抱歉
For what I did to you.
很抱歉我这样对你
I have many,many regrets,but that's the biggest.
我有很多很多后悔的事情 但这是最深的
it does not help me right now
现在这么说 对我一点用也没有
I'm sorry for that,too.
这点我也很抱歉
I didn't expect you to,uh...
我没有期望你...
I didn't expect you forgive me.
没有指望你能原谅我
But I don't want you,to,uh...
但我不希望你...
I don't want you to be alone in this.
我不希望看到 你独自面对这一切
I don't want to be alone.
我不想独自面对
let's go.
我们走
get into the car
上车
You can't get out this way.go back is the only way out of here
这条路走不通 只有往回才能出去
xxxx
那我们就往回走
Hold on.just hold on
抓好 抓好
micheal,what r u doing? just hold on
- Micheal 你要干什么? - 你只要抓好
come on
来吧
micheal
Micheal
u alright?
没事吧?
He's still behind us.
他还跟着我们
hold on
坐好
On your feet,bagwell.
起来 Bagwell
Skewers are hot.
签子已经烧热了
he's got a key
他有把钥匙
I'm going to get that key if i have to...
别逼我 快把钥匙交出来...
we're going to see that key again,friend.
我们会再看到那把钥匙的,朋友
We're going to see it real soon.
很快就能看到
Give me my credit card.
把信用卡还给我
What did you get me?
给我买了什么?
What did you get?
你买了什么?
Prune juice,smokes,a little dip,and a bag of sliders.
李子汁,烟,调味蘸酱, 还有汉堡
What do you want first?
你想先要哪个?
Looks like a chew guy to me.
我看这家伙很想吃
No spitting.
不许吐
He's had worse things in his mouth.
不会的 他嘴里还有更重要的东西
what do you want,fernando,from the future?
Fernando,未来你有什么打算?
Would you run if I said you?
我告诉你后,你会跑么?
Would you chase me if I did?
假如我跑,你会追么?
we got to get back to my car.
我们要回到我的车那儿
It's too far.
太远了
If we go now,before he gets more people...
他叫人来前走还来得及
he's not gonna call for backup.
他不会叫增援的
he wants his privacy.
他想私下里处理这件事
Why?
为什么?
He's not trying to catch me.
他不是想来抓我
He's trying to kill me.
而是想干掉我
Your grandfather.
你祖父
He was the reason I was set up in the first place.
我最初被人陷害就是因为他
He used to work for the people who wanted me dead.
他过去曾经为那些 想要置我于死地的人卖命
This is all just to get to him.
这一切都是为了抓住他
Your father should be arriving any minute.
你父亲马上就到
Jane,right?
你叫Jane是吧?
Sorry.
抱歉
Don't worry about it.
不要紧
You know my dad?
你认识我爸爸?
Well?
很熟?
Well enough.
是的
We used to work together.
我们以前一起工作
Ah,the company.
啊,那个公司
Yeah.
是的
But that was a long time ago.
可那是很久以前了
And now I work against them,just like he does.
现在我跟他一样,跟他们作对
So I guess you walked out on your family,too.
我猜你也抛弃了自己的家人
No explanations,no good-byes. I don't have a family.
- 没有解释,没有告别 - 我没有家
Lincoln,he really wants to see you and your brother.
Lincoln他真的很想见你和你弟弟
He hasn't seen michael since he was ten years old.
他上次见到Michael 还是在他10岁的时候
They're here.
他们到了
Wait here.
在这等着
let's go
快跑
Where are we going?
我们干嘛走?
Michael never met your grandfather.
Michael从来没有见过你爷爷
Hey!
嘿!
Dad.
爸
I don't want to get trapped in here.
我不想被困在这里
There's got to be an exit on the other side.
在那边应该有个出口
You go on. Michael.
- 你先走 - Michael
i'll be right behind u.Go.
我马上跟过来 快走
the news is not good. Burrows was intercepted before I got here.
消息不容乐观 我到这之前Burrows就被劫走了
It is a setback, but we're not that far behind.
糟糕 但是我想没走多远
Paul,paul,calm down.
Paul Paul 冷静点
It'll be all right. Someone will take care of it.
会没事的 有人会处理这件事
Someone... who?
有人... 是谁?
Bill,tell me you're not bringing someone else in on this.
Bill 别跟我说你还要让别人掺乎进来
You didn't think you were alone on this,did you?
你不会以为就派了你自己吧?
You're a soldier. There's an army.
你只是个士兵 我们是只部队
Tell me,what do you have on sara tancredi?
说说 你有什么Sara Tancredi的新消息没?
What does that have to do with this?
那跟这件事情有什么关系?
Go back to your original assignment.
回去处理你原来的任务吧
Bill,I'm here now. I can do this, and then... the girl.
- Bill 我在这里 我可以处理这件事 - 还是那个女孩吧
We need to know what her father told her.
我们需要知道她爸跟她说了什么
When you find out,give me a call.
你找到答案之后 打电话给我
This is agent kellerman. I need that rental car information on sara tancredi.
我是Kellerman探员 我需要Sara Tancredi租用车辆的信息
Yeah,this is it right here.
耶 就是它了
75-foot twin diesel azimut,
75尺双柴油机Azimut游艇
flybridge,panoramics, you pull up in a boat like that,you're somebody.
全景的驾驶桥楼 能坐上这种游艇 你就是大人物了
- Let me see. - Get off.
- 让我看看 - 一边儿去
how ya doin',bagwell?
怎么样? Bagwell
Get the stool.
把大便拿出来
- What stool? - The stool.
- 什么? - 大便
It's from one of them lockers in a bus station.
是车站里存物柜上的钥匙
I'll try not to think about where it's been.
我尽量不去想它是从哪里出来的
911 Calling...
呼叫911
no,no,no,no-- don't do that,now. Come on.
别 别 别 不要这样 求你了
Hey,there. Send the police. Some scumbag broke into my house.
你好 我要报警 一个坏蛋闯进我家
Yeah,1505 marberry hill.
- 你的地址? - Marberry Hill 1505号
- Is he still there? - Yeah,you better come quick.
- 他还在那儿吗? - 是的 快点来吧
let's hit it,roy.
我们走 Roy
Come on,now,please don't do this.
求你了 不要这样
Don't-- just don't leave me like this,okay?
别... 别把我丢在这里 行不?
I can take you right to the money, I know right where it is.
我可以带你们找到钱 我知道在哪儿
So do I. Adios.
我也知道 再见
I'm begging you,don't do this. Please!
求求你了 不要这样!
Geary,come on,we can make a deal, man. Come on,come on.
Geary 拜托 我们可以做个交易 求你了
No deals.
没有交易
You just crapped out your last bargaining chip,pal.
你放弃了最后的筹码 伙计
Please!
求你了!
I wouldn't do that if I were you,alex.
如果我是你我不会那样做的 Alex
You smell that?
闻到了吗?
It's propane.
是丙烷
It's filling the room.
充满了屋子
And if you pull that trigger,we both die.
你扣动扳机 咱俩都会挂
I'll do it. I'll do it!
我要杀了你 我要杀了你
Maybe.
也许吧
But before you do,let me ask you a question,alex.
不过在开枪之前 我想问你个问题 Alex
Do you think you're still one of the good guys fighting the good fight?
你认为你还是为正义而战的好人吗?
Because I think we both know you've crossed over.
我们都知道你不是
You're on the wrong,side chasing the wrong guys.
你选择了错误的立场 选择了错误的人
My brother is innocent. He never killed anyone.
我哥哥是无辜的 他没有杀人
Oh,thanks for opening my eyes.
噢 多谢你指点迷津
Okay,alex,shoot.
好吧 Alex 开枪吧
We both know what will happen.
我们都知道会有什么后果
The propane will kill me anyway,what difference does it make? Might as well do it right now.
无论怎样丙烷都会弄死我 有什么区别呢? 倒不如早点完事
That's a good point.
很有说服力
there. There!
那  那
That'll give you some time to think about what you're doing.
可以给你点时间考虑一下你所做的
But first,a word of advice: Stop.
但是首先给你一个建议 停止
Because when you get close,I will win every time.
因为每次你接近目标 我都会赢
You think?
你这么认为?
- I'm not the one in the cage. - No,you're not.
- 我不是在笼子里那个 - 是 你不在
There's one big difference between you and I,michael.
Michael 你和我有个很大的区别
And you just proved it.
而你刚刚证明了它
You can't kill.
你不会杀人
And that's what it's gonna take to stop me.
要我罢手你不得不杀人
'Cause I don't have the same reservations.
因为我不会那么仁慈
I can'T.
我不能
So whether it's today in gila  or tomorrow in albuquerque or two months from now... in panama.
所以不管是今天你在Gila 还是明天在Albuquerque 或两月后在巴拿马
I will get you.
我都会找到你
I don't have a choice.
我别无选择
I bought us some time.
我赢得了点时间
You okay? You're bleeding.
你还好吗? 你流血了
Yeah,let's go.
还好 走
Your seatbelt.
系好安全带
TRIBURE.KANSAS
Tribure 堪萨斯州
Here. 804.
是这个 804号
Move.
走开
Ain't that the most beautiful thing you ever seen?
这不就是我们看到过最漂亮的东西?
All that green.
绿绿的
It's prettier than the grand canyon.
比科罗拉多河的大峡谷都漂亮
You know,roy,this is a monumental moment for both of us.
Roy 这是我们值得纪念的时刻
Hand over the bag,bellick.
把包给我 Bellick
Put down the pounder,grandma.
放下你的破杵 "老奶奶"
Hey,hey. I am not kidding around.
嘿 嘿 没跟你开玩笑
Well,you think your pansy ass...
你以为你这个娘娘腔...
Next time,you pick through the crap.
下一次 你去弄别人的屎
Okay,first-aid kit,disposable phones, couple of toothbrushes.
好的 急救箱 一次性电话 几只牙刷
What about the motel?
汽车旅馆怎么样?
They charge by the hour, so they didn't ask for id.
他们按小时收费 所以他们不问你的身份
- Do you have the keys? - Yeah.
- 你有钥匙? - 有
Sorry,we're not home. Leave a message at the beep and we'll get back to you.
对不起 家里没人 请在"嘟"声后留言 我们会回电话
Listen. Is message is for maricruz.
听着 这是给Maricruz的留言
I was right there waiting for your call,
我一直在那等你电话
but the cops showed up and i couldn't pick up the phone.
但警察来了 我没法接
I know probably that's the exact reason why you may not want to be with me.
也许这正是 你不想和我在一起的原因
Listen to me.
听我说
My aunt idalyz,she lives outside mexico city,
我姑妈Ldalyz就住在墨西哥城外
in the mountains,on a farm,with... with a llama for the baby to ride.
那儿位于群山之中 有农场... 孩子们还可以骑美洲驼
So,next week,when you fly back home, when you go to the airport,I'll be there.
下周你飞回来的时候 我会在机场等着你
In the airport. In ixtapa I'll wait for you.
伊斯坦帕机场 我等你
I promise you,marita.
我向你保证 Marita
I love you,mari.I love you more than anything and I can't live without you.
我爱你 Mari 我爱你胜过一切 没有你我不能活
I just know I can make it work,baby.
我能成功的 宝贝
This is,uh,in case you run into trouble down the road.
这个给你 万一路上遇到麻烦 打开来看
I have a way.
我有办法了
- Where is she? - Who?
- 她在哪? - 谁?
Maricruz. She wasn't home and she's not at work.
Maricruz 她不在家 也没上班
Well,she's not here. I don't know where she is.
她不在这 我不知道她在哪
You want problems,kalinda? Don't lie to me.
你想惹祸上身吗 Kalinda? 别骗我
She went to mexico,didn't she?
她去墨西哥了 对吧?
And on our honeymoon.
在我们的蜜月之期
Paid for with my money.
花的是我的钱
This isn't gonna feel good.
可能会有点疼
I have a high tolerance for pain. You know that.
我不怕疼 你知道的
You do.
确实
And you're not a diabetic,are you?
你没有糖尿病 对吧?
All right.
是的
Michael,tell me something.
Michael 告诉我
You think there's a part of you that enjoys this?
你是不是喜欢这样?
Peroxide in an open wound? No.
在伤口上涂消毒水?  不
I mean escaping from prison
我是说越狱
and being on the run and the danger and the fear and the rush,all that.
逃亡 危险 恐惧 所有这一切
It,uh...
呃...
it feels to me likE... chasing a high.
让我感觉好像是在... 寻求刺激
And... and I know what that's like and...
而我... 知道那种感觉...
I should know better by now.
现在越发了解了
I never thought about it like that.
我从来没有这样想
I know you've heard this before, but it won't always be like this.
我知道你以前听说过什么 可一切都会好起来的
From everything you've told me, it's just getting worse.
从你告诉我的事情来看 情况越来越糟了
They can't chase us forever.
他们不可能永远追捕我们
The guy who caught up with us today,he stops at the border,and that's why we have to get across.
今天追上我们的那个人 到了边境 就得停下来 所以我们必须过境
And I have the people in place to help us do that. We're meeting them tomorrow.
我安排了人接应我们 明天就去见他们
One more day,sara.
只要再等一天 Sara
One more day.
再等一天吧
That's all I'm asking.
我只有这一个请求
You can go get cleaned up.
你可以去洗洗了
Keep this dry.
这里别打湿了
Sara.
Sara
I'm glad you came.
很高兴你能来
So...
这...
- this is him. - Lincoln,jr.
- 就是他 - Lincoln, JR
- You named him after yourself. - I wasn't gonna name him aldo.
- 跟你姓的 - 我不想让他姓Aldo
Lj,this is your grandfather,aldo burrows.
LJ 这是你爷爷 Aldo Burrows
Waited for this for a long time.
这一刻我等了很久
I've arranged a safe place for both of you to go to.
我给你们安排了一个安全的去处
Well,thanks for bailing us out, but,uh,we got to meet michael.
谢谢你解救我们 但我得去见Michael
Where is he?
他在哪?
Down by the border,a place called bolshoi booze.
他到了边境 一个叫Bolshoi Booze的地方
- I can go alone and get him. - No.
- 我可以单独去找他 - 不行
Things are different. There's some evidence.
情况变了 我们获得了一些证据
We just need a little more time,and we can blow this whole thing wide open...
我们只需要再多一点时间 一切就会水落石出...
but there is no time. I trust michael
但没有时间了 我相信michael
he has a plan to get us to panama.
他计划去巴拿马
You don't understand.
你不明白
You don't need to go to panama.
你们不需要去巴拿马
You don't need to run anymore.
你们不需要再跑了
Tell me good news.
告诉我好消息
I got burrows-- the trifecta.
我找到Burrows... 一箭三雕
- Take care of them. - What about scofield? They're gonna meet him.
- 收拾他们 - Scofield怎么办? 他们要去见他
It doesn't matter.
没关系
Do it now.
下手吧
sara?
Sara?
hi,sara.
你好 Sara